IN THE REPORT
THREE OBSERVERS
NOW / PAST / FUTURE
IN THE REPORT
PROPOSED PROCEDURE
PROPOSED
9 JUNE 1983
DOCUMENTED
DISTORTION
IN THE REPORT
CIA ARCHIVE COPY
DOCUMENTED
U.S. ARMY → CIA READING ROOM → GOVINFO
DEPARTMENT OF THE ARMY
DOCUMENTED
FORT MEADE
WAYNE M. McDONNELL
DOCUMENTED
MECHANISM / PRACTICALITY
FORT MEADE - 2009
DOCUMENTED
RECONSTRUCTION
CONTEXT RECONSTRUCTION
ARMY ASSESSMENT
DOCUMENTED
LEFT 400 Hz
RIGHT 410 Hz
DOCUMENTED
PERCEIVED BEAT 10 Hz
BINAURAL BEAT
RESEARCH
RECONSTRUCTION
CONTEXT RECONSTRUCTION
LATER PATENT - 1993
DOCUMENTED
REPORT MODEL
IN THE REPORT
HEMISPHERIC SYNCHRONIZATION
ALTERED STATE
RESEARCH
CONCEPTUAL MODEL
MODEL OF AUTHOR
ITZHAK BENTOV
IN THE REPORT
RESONANCE
MODEL OF AUTHOR
BODY / FIELD
CONSCIOUSNESS
MODEL OF AUTHOR
HOLOGRAPHIC ANALOGY
REPORT MODEL
MODEL OF AUTHOR
SPACE / TIME
THE ABSOLUTE
MODEL OF AUTHOR
FOCUS 10 / FOCUS 12
IN THE REPORT
CONCEPTUAL MODEL
MODEL OF AUTHOR
NEXT: 15 / 21
IN THE REPORT
TRAVEL INTO THE PAST
CONCEPTUAL MODEL
CLAIMED
LESS THAN 5% - IN REPORT
IN THE REPORT
FOCUS 15 - PAST
THE FUTURE
IN THE REPORT
FOCUS 21 - FUTURE
RECONSTRUCTION
CLAIMED
NO GUARANTEE - IN REPORT
IN THE REPORT
DOCUMENTED / CLAIMED
SUMMARY
IN THE REPORT
INFORMATION COLLECTION POTENTIAL
DISTORTION
IN THE REPORT
ONE TARGET
NORMAL SPACE-TIME
IN THE REPORT
FOCUS 15
FOCUS 21
IN THE REPORT
COMPARE DATA
PROPOSED - NOT A RESULT
PROPOSED
PROPOSED STEPS
IN THE REPORT
NON-CORPOREAL ENERGY FORMS
PROPOSED - NOT PROVEN
IN THE REPORT
AUDITORY TEST
RESEARCH
SYSTEMATIC REVIEW - 2023
BINAURAL / MONAURAL
RESEARCH FIGURE
14 EEG STUDIES
RESEARCH
5 SUPPORT / 8 CONTRADICT / 1 MIXED
HETEROGENEOUS METHODS
RESEARCH
ALTERED STATE
PAST / FUTURE INFORMATION
CLAIMED
RECONSTRUCTION
VERIFY NEW INFORMATION
OPEN
THE CLAIM GAP
SUMMARY
REPORT EXISTS
DOCUMENTED
ARMY ASSESSMENT
CLAIMS IN REPORT
CLAIMED
OPERATIONAL RELIABILITY: OPEN
OPEN
NOT CIA PROOF
SUMMARY
PAST / PRESENT / FUTURE
IN THE REPORT
THE IMPOSSIBLE - PLANNED ON PAPER
SUMMARY